onecallnow.com 2009-06-24

# One Call Now | Privacy Policy

##  One Call Now's Privacy Policy 

Our Privacy Policy affects and protects both You as our client, and your Members. 

Except as set forth herein, One Call Now never has and never will sell, lease, rent or give any personal information including names, addresses, phone numbers or email addresses about You or your Members to any third party. 

"Members" to us may be, but are not limited to, Members of your group receiving notification messages sent by you through One Call Now such as your players, congregation, staff, citizens, customers or residents. 

"YOU" refers to you, our Client, acting as Group Administrator and responsible for managing personal information entered on or uploaded to our website and used by you, or people you designate to contact Members of your group and to see the results of those messages. 

"Group" refers to you as an individual or your organization, using the One Call Now service to send notification messages to your Members. 

This Policy applies to MyTeam1, LLC, doing business as One Call Now. References throughout this Policy to "One Call Now", "We", "Our" and "Us" are treated identically. References to "Client", "You" or "Your" are treated interchangeably.   
  
---  
What Is Personal Information?   
Personal information is any information that identifies you or your members as individuals. Personal information includes names, addresses, phone numbers, e-mail addresses, and identification numbers; the content of messages sent from you to your members; your financial information, such as credit card or checking account information, either from you or your organization. For some services, this may include cell phone provider, street address, member identification number, and other information to properly segment them for certain notification calls. 

Why Does One Call Now Ask For Personal Information?   
In order to properly handle the billing for your account, we need credit card, checking account or other financial information. In order to deliver voice, text and e-mail messages to your Members, we need means to identify them and segment them for certain notification calls. 

How Does One Call Now Safeguard My Personal Information And Keep It Confidential?   
Each and every one of our employees is responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of all personal information to which they have access. We run an array of background, criminal, and financial checks on every employee, and all employees are subject to random drug testing; all in an effort to protect your privacy and information as best we can. As a condition of employment, our employees are required to sign a confidentiality agreement that binds them to this responsibility-- even after they leave One Call Now. We keep our employees informed about our policies and procedures for protecting personal information and reinforce the importance of compliance. 

In addition, One Call Now has comprehensive security controls to protect against the unauthorized use, alteration, duplication, destruction, disclosure, loss or theft of-and unauthorized access to-your personal information. When we receive personal information about you or your members (such as name, address, phone number and credit card number), it is stored on our secure servers. 

We ensure the physical, organizational and electronic security of your personal information through the use of secure locks on filing cabinets and doors, restricted access to information processing and storage areas, limited access to relevant information by authorized employees only, and passwords, PINs, pass keys and the SSL Certificates in place to ensure data encryption or scrambling of electronically transmitted information. We follow standard internet and database security practices and keep up-to-date with industry changes. All financial and password data is stored in encrypted form on our databases. We also have strict procedures in place for destruction, deletion or disposal of personal information when it is no longer required for the purposes set out in this Policy-or by law-to prevent unauthorized access to such information. 

We may use other companies to provide services to you on our behalf. In such cases, we have agreements in place that hold these companies to the same high standards of confidentiality by which we are governed and require that any information provided by us be kept strictly confidential and used only for the purposes stated in the agreement. 

One Call Now Has A Strict Policy Of Not Releasing Personal Information About Our Clients Or Their Members Unless:

|  1\.  |  You have consented to the release of personal information. For example, you or your members are part of a larger organization and want them to be able to reach you.  
---|---  
2\.  |  We have a legal obligation. For example, we may release personal information about a client to legal authorities in cases of the public's interest, criminal activity or the detection and prevention of fraud.  
  
If we release information for any of these reasons, we keep a record of what, when, why and to whom such information was released. 

Under no circumstances do we sell, rent or give lists of our clients or their members to others for their use 

How Does One Call Now Keep Your Personal Information Accurate?   
One Call Now is committed to maintaining the accuracy of your and your members' personal information for as long as it is being used for the purposes set out in this policy, and you play an active role in keeping us up-to-date. 

Prompt notification of any changes-for example, to your address, e-mail address or telephone number-will help us provide the best possible service. Please advise us if you discover, upon review of your or your Members' personal information, that amendments are required. 

How Can You Access Your or Your Members' Personal Information?   
If you want to review or verify your or your members' personal information-or find out to whom we have disclosed it, as permitted by this Policy-please contact us. 

In Some Instances, We May Not Be Able To Grant Your Request, Such As If The Personal Information:   
Contains references to other persons 

* |  Is subject to attorney-client or litigation privilege   
---|---  
* |  Includes our own proprietary and confidential information   
* |  Has been destroyed due to legal requirements or because it was no longer needed for the purposes set out in this Policy   
* |  Is too costly, in our determination, to retrieve   
* |  Cannot be disclosed for legal reasons.   
  
If we are unable to provide access to your or your Members' personal information, we will provide you with an explanation. 

Does One Call Now Retain Your Personal Information and/or that of my members?   
One Call Now keeps your, and your Members, personal information for as long as it is needed to meet the purposes set out in this Policy. The length of time we retain your personal information is also affected by: (1) the type of service you have with us, and (2) any legal requirements we may have to meet. In addition, we have retention policies in place that govern the destruction of personal information. 

Acquisition of One Call Now   
In the event that One Call Now, or substantially all of its assets are acquired, you consent to the transfer of your information as one of the transferred assets, to be used only as defined and under the limits outlined above. 

Privacy Policy for One Call Now Notification Solutions 02/10/2009
